Fragment的最后一个好处与用户界面完全无关
The final advantage of fragments, doesn't involve user interfaces at
你知道的。如你所知，作为可视元件，Activity会在设备配置
all. As you know, as visual components, activities are destroyed and
发生任何变化的时候被销毁然后重建。最常见的是
re-created, whenever the device configuration changes. Most notably, when the
当屏幕转向时。这很合理，因为我们很
screen orientation switches. That makes sense, because there's a good chance
有可能希望创建一个不同的布局来适应
we'll want to create a different layout, to better suit the
新的配置。但是如果我们可以使用Fragment来
new configuration. But if we can use fragments to break up
打碎视觉上的Activity模块，而找出逻辑上的模块，
visual activity modules, and find out logical ones as well,
事实证明我们完全可以做到。并且因为这些
it turns out we can do exactly that. And because these
Fragment是不可视的，也就不需要重新创建它们
fragments are non-visual, there's no need to recreate them
每当用户界面需要更新时。在不可视的Fragment的
every time the UI needs updating. Within the onCreate
onCreate函数里，调用setRetainInstance，传入true，
handler of your non-UI fragment, call setRetainInstance, passing in
并且让onCreateView函数返回null
true, and return null in your onCreateView handler.
然后只要它所属的Activity一创建好，
Then, once the parent activity is created, you can
你就可以断掉它们之间的任何联系，包括
kick off any connections, threads, or tasks that are
与这个Activity生命周期联系在一起的Thread或Task
bound to the lifetime of the activity, which don't
不需要每次设备转向时都被中断
need to be interrupted every time the device rotates.